ALEX J HARTLAUB

Alexhartlaub15@gmail.com ~ Naperville, IL ~ 630.877.7740

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Customer Service: 1 year of experience assisting customers, problem-solving, and resolving escalated issues **Communication:** Interpersonal, collaboration, and presentation skills with people of diverse backgrounds **Leadership:** Learned how to be a leader through 4+ years of team sports.

Research: Skilled in gathering and analyzing internal/external data in a variety of environments

EDUCATION

Expected: May 2023 GPA: 3.2/4.0 **Bachelor of Arts in Computer science** Lewis University, Romeoville, IL

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer server desk

American Sale, Naperville, IL

December 2012 - 2014

- Assist diverse array of customers with their selections and purchases
 Process 30+ cash and credit transactions daily; balance cash drawer
 Enter daily revenue from registers into excel file

- · Resolve customer complaints to ensure satisfaction and promote repeat business

General Worker

Hart erectors INC, Naperville, IL

July 2014 - Present

- Manage warehouse, including stock management, recycling, and sorting
- Update 30+ bleacher inspection reports per year
- · Quote prices on inspection and or maintenance jobs
- Send emails to customers and answer phone calls

Golf Course Sand Trap Worker

Hart erectors INC, Naperville, IL

May 2022 - present

· Sand trap repair and maintenance

SUMMARY OF TECHNICAL QUALIFICATIONS

Operating Systems:

· Windows, Linux, iOS

Networking:

· LAN, WAN, Wireless, Cisco Networking Academy

Languages:

• C, C++, C#, Java, Python

Web:

• HTML

Applcations:

· Microsoft Office, Photoshop, Google Docs, Spreadsheets, Quickbooks, MySQL

Hardware / Systems:

• PC, Mac, Backup, Cloud management, Security systems, Network Configuration, CISCO

LANGUAGES SKILLS

- · Fluent in japanese
- Semi-fluent in Spanish